Richard Rodgers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-18, Box 22-45)
  - Full scores (Box 22-45)
    - Flower Drum Song (1958) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Chop suey encore, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 29/1)
      - Don't marry me, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 22 p. (Box-folder 29/2)
      - Encore -- Don't marry, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p. (Box-folder 29/2)
      - Entr'acte: act II, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 29/3)
      - Intro: Fan Tan Fanny, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p.; Uniform title: Fan Tan Fannie (Box-folder 29/4)
      - Fan Tan Fanny: opening scene 7, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 8 p.; Uniform title: Fan Tan Fannie (Box-folder 29/4)
      - Finale act two, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 29/5)
      - Finale ultimo II, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink & orange pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 29/5)
      - Memoree; New ending (Grant Ave.), Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink & orange & blue pencil; 22 p.; Uniform title: Gliding through my memoree (Box-folder 29/6)
      - Grant Avenue, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 15 p. + p. 8a-8b, 151⁄2; Note: not used in show (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Grant Avenue, Arranger's holograph (Luther Henderson) full score in pencil; 16 p.; Note: not used in show (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Grant Ave: insert, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 5 p.; Note: not used in show (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Grant Ave: exit, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in pencil; [3] p.; Note: part of assortment labelled "Outtakes" (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Grant Avenue for Anita, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Grant Avenue IV, Arrangers' holograph (Bennett; Joe Glover) full score in ink pencil; [33] p. (various paginations) (Box-folder 29/8)
      - Grant Avenue: new new, Arrangers' holograph (Joe Glover, p. 1-10; Bennett, p. 26-31) full score in ink & red pencil; [16] p.; Note: part of assortment labelled "Outtakes" (Box-folder 29/9)
      - A hundred million miracles, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 29 p. + 2nd p. 14 + [1] p. ending (Box-folder 29/10)
      - Miracles encore, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 29/10)
      - I am going to like it here, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 13 p. + 2nd p. [1] (Box-folder 30/1)
      - I enjoy being a girl, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 23 p. (Box-folder 30/2)
      - Encore: I enjoy being a girl, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 19 p. (Box-folder 30/2)
      - New 2nd refrain: Being a girl, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 30/2)
      - Like a god: verse; Like a god, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full scores in ink; 3 p.; 10 p. (Box-folder 30/3)
      - 2nd refrain and encore, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 13 p. (Box-folder 30/3)
      - New intro: Love, look away, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 1 p.; Uniform title: Love, look away (Box-folder 30/4)
      - Love, look away: verse & chorus, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [10] p.; Note: "out" is inscribed at the beginning and end of verse section; Uniform title: Love, look away (Box-folder 30/4)
      - Reprise: Love, look away, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p. + [1] p. ending; Uniform title: Love, look away (Box-folder 30/4)
      - Replacing 1st ten bars: Reprise -- Love, look away, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p.; Uniform title: Love, look away (Box-folder 30/4)
      - My best love, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 15 p.; On folder: "Not used!" (Box-folder 30/5)
      - Best love E[-flat]: new; End of rep. My best love, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 8 p.; 2 p.; On folder: "Not used!" (Box-folder 30/5)
      - My best love reprise, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink & pencil; 7 p.; On t.p.: "Out!" (Box-folder 30/5)
      - Opening act one, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p. (Box-folder 30/6)
      - Opening act two, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 30/7)
      - The other generation, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 12 p.; On folder: "Reprise: The other generation" (Box-folder 30/8)
      - Other generation -- dance, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 13 p. (Box-folder 30/8)
      - Other gen. reprise, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 7 p. + [5] p. insert (Box-folder 30/8)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 26 p. + 10 p. insert (Box-folder 30/9)
      - She is beautiful see: You are beautiful
      - Sunday: Khyber -- Suzuki; New Sunday dance; 2nd refrain Sunday, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full scores in ink; 10 p.; 17 p. + [1] p. insert + p. 11-15; 6 p. (Box-folder 31/1)
      - Sunday: [B-flat], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencils; 11 p.; Note: part of assortment labelled "Outtakes" (Box-folder 31/1)
      - Sunday dance: [act II], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 12 p. + [3] p. (inserts); Note: includes insert titled "Suzy's Sunday" (Box-folder 31/1)
      - Opening Ta's dream: #16, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p.; Uniform title: Ta's dream (Box-folder 31/2)
      - Ta's dream: [ballet], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 36 p.; Laid in: note which reads "Print New End Ta's Dream"; Uniform title: Ta's dream (Box-folder 31/2)
      - New end Ta's dream, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p.; Uniform title: Ta's dream (Box-folder 31/2)
      - Coda: Ta's dream; Night with Helen: end of coda Ta's dream, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p.; 2 p.; Uniform title: Ta's dream (Box-folder 31/2)
      - She is the girl, or, You are beautiful, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 15 p.; Uniform title: You are beautiful (Box-folder 31/3)
      - Reprise: She is beautiful, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p.; Uniform title: You are beautiful (Box-folder 31/3)
      - Act I reprise: Beautiful, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p.; Uniform title: You are beautiful (Box-folder 31/3)
      - Act II reprise: Beautiful, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p.; Uniform title: You are beautiful (Box-folder 31/3)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores I], Arrangers' holograph (Bennett; Joe Glover) full scores in ink; Includes: Hundred million utilities: #2 Bridge 1-1: Bridge to scene 2: #2-(a) End of scene 2: #4 Bridge after "Girl": Bridge to scene 3: #4(a) Back beating: #5 Bridge 1-3: #6a Bridge to scene 5: #7(a) (Box-folder 31/4)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores II], Arrangers' holograph (Bennett; Joe Glover) full scores in ink & pencil; Includes: Like a god utility: 7a Jazz bit: #9 Bridge 1-5: #11-a Bridge after 17: scene 2 act II: #17-a Sunday utility: #20 Procession: #23 Wedding cross: Procession: #23 (Box-folder 31/5)
      - [Miscellaneous unused music], Arrangers' holograph (Bennett; Joe Glover) full scores in ink; Includes: Best love utility Bridge to scene 3 Replacing last two bars Chaser [You are beautiful]: She is the utility (Box-folder 31/6)
    - The King and I (1951) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Entr'acte, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 32/1)
      - Finale act I, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 32/2)
      - Getting to know you, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 32/3)
      - School room dance: #15-a, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: laid in between p. 12 & 13 of "Getting to know you" (Box-folder 32/3)
      - Hello, young lovers, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & blue pencil; 13 p. (Box-folder 32/4)
      - I have dreamed, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 9 p. (Box-folder 32/5)
      - Intro. I have dreamed, Arranger's holograph full score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 32/5)
      - I whistle [a happy tune], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 13 p. + p. 10a, 10b (Box-folder 32/6)
      - Children's march, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 17 p. + p. 17/a; Uniform title: March of the royal Siamese children (Box-folder 32/7)
      - Postlude Children's march, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 5 p.; Uniform title: March of the royal Siamese children (Box-folder 32/7)
      - Parade: 44, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full score in ink; p. 1-7, 16-19; Uniform title: March of the royal Siamese children (Box-folder 32/7)
      - Lord and master, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p. + [1] p. insert; Note: reduced negative photostat of the above enclosed; Uniform title: My lord and master (Box-folder 32/8)
      - Lord and master: melos act two, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 1 p.; Uniform title: My lord and master (Box-folder 32/8)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [36] p. (variously paginated); Note: includes section titled "Dreamed in overture" (Box-folder 32/9)
      - [A] puzzlement, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 28 p. (Box-folder 32/10)
      - Boy's puzzlement: 18, 18a, Ms. and arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [19] p. (variously paginated) (Box-folder 32/10)
      - School song, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p.; Uniform title: The Royal Bangkok Academy (Box-folder 33/1)
      - Intro -- bedroom, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p.; Uniform title: Shall I tell you what I think of you? (Box-folder 33/2)
      - Anna's bedroom, or, Shall I tell you what I think of you, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 26 p.; Uniform title: Shall I tell you what I think of you? (Box-folder 33/2)
      - Shall we dance?, Arranger's holograph (Don Walker) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: p. 14, in Bennett's hand is titled "Polka E-flat strain" (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Shall we dance: march 1, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Shall we dance at H, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [9] p.; Note: the last 2 pages are titled "Chaser" (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Shall we dance (album), Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 1 p. (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Shall we -- encore bar 6, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. a-b (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Uncle Tom: ballet, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink and pencils; 79 p.; Uniform title: The small house of Uncle Thomas ballet (Box-folder 33/4)
      - Postlude of ballet, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 7 p.; Uniform title: The small house of Uncle Thomas ballet (Box-folder 33/4)
      - Something wonderful, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full score in ink; p. 1-6, 3-12; Note laid in: "Last 12 bars missing" (Box-folder 33/5)
      - Something wonderful, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; 8 p. (Box-folder 33/5)
      - Wonderful coda: change of scene, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 33/5)
      - Scene and We kiss, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 16 p.; Uniform title: We kiss in a shadow (Box-folder 33/6)
      - We kiss -- 2nd refrain: encore: #17, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score; 10 p.; Uniform title: We kiss in a shadow (Box-folder 33/6)
      - Western people funny, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 33/7)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores], Arrangers' holograph (Bennett; Hans Spialek; Don Walker) full scores in ink; Includes: Arrival at Bangkok: no. 2 Vignettes & dance: 6 [Don Walker score] So big a world: 16 After reprise [Something] wonderful: 22 Anna and King planning party: 24 Fireworks: 25 Varsovienne: Dance of Anna & Sir Edward: 30 Curtain raiser: act II Evil eye: exit of wives (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Oklahoma! (1943) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - All er nothin', Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 49 p.; On t.p.: "Out" (Box-folder 34/1)
      - Entr'acte, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink, photocopy and pencil ms. inserts; 9 p. + inserts (7 p. & [2] p.); Note: 7 p. insert is "Many a new day (Utility)" (Box-folder 34/2)
      - Opening act II, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencils; [63] p. (variously paginated); Note: includes "Dance"; Uniform title: The farmer and the cowman (Box-folder 34/3)
      - [Finale ultimo], Ms. full score in pencil (p. 1-8) and arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencils (p. 6-14); [17] p. (Box-folder 34/4)
      - Cain't say no -- intro., Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p.; Uniform title: I cain't say no (Box-folder 34/5)
      - I can't say no, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencils; 24 p.; Laid in: note and photocopy regarding encore of "I cain't say no" (Box-folder 34/5)
      - 1st reprise Can't say no, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; p. 1-4, 1-2; Note: includes "New bridge in reprise 'Can't say no'"; Uniform title: I cain't say no (Box-folder 34/5)
      - [I cain't say no], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 5-7, 9; Note: probably cut section; originally part of "1st reprise" (Box-folder 34/5)
      - 2nd reprise Can't say no, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-8 (incomplete); Uniform title: I cain't say no (Box-folder 34/5)
      - Scandal for jaybirds; Scandal exit, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencils and ms. full score in pencil; 35 p.; Uniform title: It's a scandal! It's a outrage! (Box-folder 34/6)
      - Kansas City, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full score in ink and pencils; [28] p. (variously paginated) (Box-folder 35/1)
      - Kansas City dance, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencils; 36 p. (Box-folder 35/1)
      - Kansas City, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 35/2)
      - Kansas City -- orch. chos., Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-7, 22-30 (Box-folder 35/2)
      - Kansas City -- intro., Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 35/2)
      - Coda -- K.C., Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 35/2)
      - Kansas City: boys chorus, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) choral score in ink; 2 p. (Box-folder 35/2)
      - Opening act II; End of act I; New end act I, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full scores in ink & pencils; [146] p. (variously paginated); 12 p.; 2 p.; Note: folder 14/3 includes p. 1-69; folder 14/4 includes p. 70-148 and endings; Uniform title: Laurey makes up her mind ballet (Box-folder 35/3-4)
      - Lonely little room, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencils; 13 p.; Uniform title: Lonely room (Box-folder 35/5)
      - Many a new day -- intro., Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 36/1)
      - Many a new day, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & green pencil; 22 p. (Box-folder 36/1)
      - Many a new day dance, Ms. full score in pencil; p. 1-7, 9-31; Note: measure numbers continuous with "Many a new day" above (Box-folder 36/1)
      - Many a new day -- last 2 bars -- replacing last bar, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 36/1)
      - Many a new day dance, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 30 p. (Box-folder 36/2)
      - Last 2 bars into Many a new day dance, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 36/2)
      - Many a new day: last 2 bars into 2d refrain, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 36/2)
      - Beautiful morning: Opening act one, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & green pencil; p. 1-22, 24-32; Uniform title: Oh, what a beautiful mornin' (Box-folder 36/3)
      - Oklahoma, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full score in ink & pencils; [54] p. (various paginations); Includes: "Oklahoma bridge" "Oklahoma (2d vocal)" empty folder for "Encore -- 'Oklahoma'" (Box-folder 36/4)
      - Opening act II see: The farmer and the cowman
      - Out of my dreams See also: Laurey makes up her mind ballet, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p. (title page) (Box-folder 36/5)
      - Out of my dreams -- intro. See also: Laurey makes up her mind ballet, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 36/5)
      - Intro: Out of my dreams See also: Laurey makes up her mind ballet, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 2 only (Box-folder 36/5)
      - Intro. to Out of my dreams See also: Laurey makes up her mind ballet, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p. (incomplete) (Box-folder 36/5)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & green pencil; 58 p. (Box-folder 36/6)
      - People will say [we're in love], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full score in ink & pencils; 28 p. (Box-folder 37/1)
      - Reprise "People will say", Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & green pencil; 12 p. (Box-folder 37/1)
      - Pore Jud is daid, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & green pencil; 15 p. (Box-folder 37/2)
      - Surrey -- intro., Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p.; On t.p.: "Not in Show"; Uniform title: The surrey with the fringe on top (Box-folder 37/3)
      - The surrey, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & green pencil; 40 p.; Uniform title: The surrey with the fringe on top (Box-folder 37/3)
      - Surrey -- reprise: #5, Ms. full score in pencil; 4 p.; Uniform title: The surrey with the fringe on top (Box-folder 37/3)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores I], Arranger's holog. (Bennett) & unident. ms. full scores in ink & pencil; Includes: Farmer dance: 13a [Laurey makes up her mind]: New bridge to Ballet Laurey's entrance: #2 Many a new day (utility): #16 [score & photocopy] [Oh, what a beautiful morning]: Morning bridge. Note: "Not used!" [Oh, what a beautiful morning]. Note: not used in show Out of my dreams (utility) (Box-folder 37/4)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores II], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full scores in ink & pencil; Includes: People will say (utility): #13 [People will say we're in love]: Out march Scene change: #21 [The surrey with the fringe on top]: Verse (orch. solo) Surrey. On t.p.: "Not in show" Surrey (utility) (Box-folder 37/5)
      - [Full score fragments -- unused], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full scores (incomplete) in ink; Includes: [All er nothin'] [It's a scandal! It's a outrage!] [People will say we're in love] (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Pipe Dream (1955) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - All at once [you love her], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 32 p.; Includes: "New end act I" (p. 23-32) (Box-folder 38/1)
      - [All at once you love her], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 23-29, 35-49; Attached note: "These pages not used" (Box-folder 38/1)
      - Verse "All at once"; All Helen's reprise, Arrangers' holograph (Bennett; Joe Glover) full score in ink; 3 p.; 9 p.; Uniform title: All at once you love her (Box-folder 38/2)
      - All at once (utility), Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 11 p.; On folder: "Reprise: 'All at once'" and "Not used!"; Uniform title: All at once you love her (Box-folder 38/2)
      - All kinds of people, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 28 p. + 4 p. insert (Box-folder 38/3)
      - People reprise I, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 7 p.; Uniform title: All kinds of people (Box-folder 38/4)
      - People reprise II, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 3 p.; On t.p.: "Not used!"; Uniform title: All kinds of people (Box-folder 38/4)
      - People reprise #2, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; p. 4-8; Uniform title: All kinds of people (Box-folder 38/4)
      - Bum's opera; New B.O., Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full scores in ink; 24 p.; 4 p. (Box-folder 38/5)
      - Part of #7 Bums opera, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 25-45, 45a; On p. 25: "Out!" (Box-folder 38/5)
      - Bums opera (utility): reprise: #9, Ms. full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 38/6)
      - Bums' new ending: Fauna's song: #8, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 19 p. (Box-folder 38/6)
      - Entr'acte, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 29 p. (Box-folder 38/7)
      - Temp entr'acte, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 38/7)
      - Everybody's got a home [but me], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; p. 1-22, 28-50 (Box-folder 38/8)
      - Everybody's got a home: utility, Ms. full score in ink; 8 p.; Note: not used in show (Box-folder 38/8)
      - Finale, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 9 p.; On t.p.: "Pipe Dream Album" and "Not used! in show" (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Finale ultimo, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 16 p. (Box-folder 39/2)
      - New finale ultimo, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 39/2)
      - Fractured fugue: dance fugue: #22-a, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 16 p. (Box-folder 39/3)
      - The happiest house [on the block], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 19 p. (Box-folder 39/4)
      - How long?, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 47 p. (Box-folder 39/5)
      - I am a witch, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 18 p.; On cover: "We are a gang of witches" (Box-folder 39/6)
      - [A] lopsided bus, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full score in ink; 66 p. + [19] p. insert (numbered variously 1-38) (Box-folder 39/7)
      - Bus reprise: #10, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [17] p. (numbered variously 1-19); Uniform title: A lopsided bus (Box-folder 39/8)
      - The man I used to be, Arrangers' holograph (Joe Glover; Bennett [insert]) full score in ink & pencil; 23 p. + 2 p. insert; Note: insert titled "Doc's essence" (Box-folder 39/9)
      - Man "incidental", Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 6 p.; On t.p.: "Not used!" (Box-folder 39/9)
      - Entrance 2 party: masquerade brawl, Ms. full score in ink; 20 p.; Uniform title: Masquerade brawl at the flophouse (Box-folder 39/10)
      - Next time, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 43 p.; Uniform title: The next time it happens (Box-folder 40/1)
      - Next time (part II), Ms. full score in ink; 13 p.; Note on p. 1: "Dr. Sirmay had this section reconstructed from parts because it was missing from the Rodgers Hammerstein office/L.S."; Uniform title: The next time it happens (Box-folder 40/1)
      - Next time curtain, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p.; On cover: "Not used"; Uniform title: The next time it happens (Box-folder 40/1)
      - The next time it happens, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 54 p.; On t.p.: "Not used!" (Box-folder 40/2)